thecinemasource.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy | The Cinema Source

[TheCinemaSource.com](http://www.thecinemasource.com/) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of [TheCinemaSource.com](http://www.thecinemasource.com/)

### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to administer our website. The IP address is only employed to help identify the user when problems occur and when solving the problem. The IP address will not be used for any other means.

### Third Party Advertising

We use Gorilla Nation and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this website and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this website, our third-party ad server, Gorilla Nation or their affiliates, or individual advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

### Personal Information

Our site’s mailing list and contest forms ask visitors to provide their email and mailing addresses. We use the contact information gathered from the form to send the visitor information about our company and about upcoming entertainment. The visitor’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Visitors may opt-out of receiving future mailings (see the “choice/opt-out” section below).

### External Links

This website contains links to other websites. [TheCinemaSource.com](http://www.thecinemasource.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

### Public Forums

This website makes message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Security

This website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. For more information about our security measures, you may [contact us.](mailto:dandeevy@thecinemasource.com)

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our website provides users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time.

### Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please [contact us.](mailto:dandeevy@thecinemasource.com)
